[Music]
hello and thank you for tuning in for
another product review from Sharps
Shooting Supply my name is Tyler sharp
and let's dive on in So today we're
going to cover the Kimber Pro Carry 2
chambered in 9 mm the uh pro carry op
option also comes in 45 ACP but this
particular one is in 9
mm and and it belongs in that 1911
family of
firearms this firearm does come in at 28
Oz empty features a 9+ 1 capacity
magazine and a 4in
barrel so with an overall length of only
7.7 in this would make one excellent
concealed carry firearm features those
beautiful Rosewood
grips a three dot sight picture on it
looks like they're not night sights but
it does have a nice three dot sight
picture on there the big thumb safety so
you've got that nice kind of oversized
thumb safety gives you plenty of areas
to hit with your thumb and it features a
skeletonized
hammer one of the things that was really
impressive about this firearm is it
features a 2B trigger so that that is
really a light trigger that's uh pretty
neat seeing on the this nice concealed
carry
firearm another cool thing is it does
feature a fulls siiz grip so there is
plenty of room for your hands to to fit
on there and I don't have massive hands
and there is plenty of room for my hand
on there with room to
spare so that's a pretty cool feature on
it it does Rack open nice and
easy and it is just an excellent firearm
right out of the
box Let's uh check out what's in the box
of course there's that youth handgun
safety
notice the Kimber registration and of
course the product owner's
manual the trigger lock looks like we've
got some uh some grease in
there stickers looks like they're trying
to sell you a holster as well and then
there is the small allen wrench in here
to adjust that rear sight right there
it's kind of neat that they give you
that allen wrench in the box cuz it is a
little
one so not a lot of accessories in the
box of course kimber's known for not
really wanting to give out that extra
mag but Kimber Pro Carry 2 9 mm
excellent firearm would be great for
concealed carry or just even a fun day
plinking at the range that 9mm is going
to be pleasant to
shoot so we do appreciate you swinging
by for this product review and we will
catch you on the next one